Guide to the International Woodworkers of America Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- International Woodworkers of America records, 1936-1942; 4000-002; 0.18 cubic feet (1 box) 1 bound volume
  This volume, bound by the Library, begins with minutes of the Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union, Local #2532, Portland, and continues as the IWA in 1937, when most of the LSMWU affiliated with the CIO. This seems to be a record of the Columbia River (?) District Council, which opposed the more radical leadership in Washington State.
  UW Libraries, Special Collections, February 08, 1991